ILGWU Boston Joint Board Records 5780/055
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Boston Joint Board Records
1969-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Boston Joint Board
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/055
28 cubic feet
28 linear ft.
Records (documents).
The collection contains meeting minutes and correspondence of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Boston Joint Board, meeting minutes for several Boston locals (12, 46, 46, 73, and 80), company files, as well as the personal correspondence of Philip Kramer.
5491494
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D. Mordente, November 19, 2008
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 08, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
Like other cities with garment work, Boston cloak workers organized early, forming the Boston Cloak Makers' Protective Union around 1890, a decade before the founding of the ILGWU. In 1907, the Boston Pressers' Local 12, Skirt and Cloak Makers' Local 13, and Cloak and Suit Cutters' Local 26 called a general strike demanding a fifty hour week and recognition of the union. While ultimately unsuccessful, the strike did lay the ground work for the Great Revolt in 1910. Later, the locals Cloak and Skirt Pressers Local 12, Skirt Makers Local 56, Cutters Local 73, Waist and Dressmakers Local 49, and Ladies' Tailors Local 36 composed the Boston Joint Board. In 1914 though, these locals were far from flourishing, and existed merely on paper with no money in their treasury. Abraham Rosenberg was appointed manager of the Joint Board to assist with the situation in Boston. During this time, a new system of shop inspections was introduced and soon the entire trade was thoroughly organized. Also established was week work as well as job placement made through the union. In 1915, the skirtmakers from Local 56 broke off and chartered a new Local 24. Rosenberg resigned in at the end of 1916. With conditions in Boston poor, the Joint Board and locals were reorganized by the International with Abraham Snyder appointed manager for 6 months, before being passed to Hyman Hurwitz. By 1919, the Joint Board was negotiating collective agreements with a newly formed manufacturers' association. Among the demands obtained were a 44 hour work week and a minimum wage scale.
A double strike of cloakmakers and dressmakers in Boston in 1923 strengthened the union's position in the city. Max Amdur was placed in charge of the Joint Board in 1928, assisted by Philip Kramer. Like the rest of the union, the Joint Board suffered from infighting among the Communist members during this time. By 1929, there was a move toward unification, and a new administration elected. The Joint Board and locals moved to new headquarters. In 1930, ILGWU vice-president Israel Feinberg was appointed manager, replacing an ill vice-president Max Amdur. Amdur returned in 1931 to manage the Joint Board but resigned later that year due to poor health and was replaced by vice-president Jacob Halpern with Kramer in charge of organizing. Philip Kramer would become the Joint Board manager in 1932, a position he would hold for the next 41 years. The 1940s saw the silk dress industry in Boston nearly all unionized, with many of the cloak and skirt branches as well, and the Joint Board was on strong financial footing. In 1942, with the assistance of the Cotton Garment Department, the Joint Board had a successful campaign in the skirt industry bringing in new members and standardizing work. Cloakmakers won vacation pay in 1942 and in 1944 there was the first collective agreement with the Associated Dress Manufacturing Inc. This time also saw the Joint Board with active interest in the Massachusetts Liberal Labor Committee, purchasing war bonds, and contributing to Red Cross work. At the end of the decade into the 1950s, the Joint Board continued to organize substantial numbers of shops, especially with the large number of new shops which opened during the war. Locals expanded to include 12 (Pressers), 33 (Skirtmakers), 39 (Finishers), 46 (Dressmakers), 56 (Cloak Operators), 73 (Cutters), and 80 (Italian Cloak, Skirt and Dressmakers). In 1947, together with the Northeast Department, the Joint Board purchased a building to house a Union Health Center.
The Joint Board became involved in labor and philanthropy causes, and collected an extra week's dues each month for charity and humanitarian relief. In the mid-1950s, the market stabilized, and firms in the cloak industry began changing from time-work to piece-work. By 1957 all retirement fundscloak, dress, sportswearwere merged. And in 1962, the Massachusetts Legislature banned industrial homework. In 1965, Boston saw shops going out of business and relocating outside of the city. New organizing efforts were no longer a priority for the Joint Board but fell to the Northeast Department. In March 1967, the Joint Board and Northeast Department struck 67 shops which had failed to sign an agreement. Philip Kramer retired as manager of the Joint Board in 1973 and Milton Kaplan was elected as the new manager. Soon, the Joint Board voted to become a part of the Northeast Department. Further reorganization after the 1977 convention formed the Northeast and Western Pennsylvania Department.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Boston Joint Board contain three series. The first series is composed of meeting minutes. The meetings are for the various locals that comprised the Boston Joint Board (Locals 12, 46, 56, 73, and 80) as well as the Joint Board itself. The early minutes are bound and hand-written. Later minutes are no longer bound and typewritten.
The second series is composed mainly of correspondence, but also contains records of the administrative function and union activities of the Joint Board. There are the meeting minutes of the various committees of the Joint Board, including the Grievance Committee, the Appeals Committee and the Negotiating Committee (with agreements). Departments of the Joint Board represented include the Health and Vacation Fund and the Retirement Fund. In addition to correspondence and records of those departments, there are also the rules and regulations. Administrative material includes finances, receipts and disbursement statements. There is much information on local executive board elections and of note is a listing of incoming members and which local they joined. The correspondence is to and from the International, office of the president (David Dubinsky), union departments and other Joint Boards. Correspondence also involves garment companies, and manufacturers and associations. Of special interest is the correspondence with the Boston City Council as well as Massachusetts members of Congress.
Most of the correspondence is to and from longtime Boston Joint Board manager Philip Kramer. Kramer came to the United States in 1905 and soon found work in a dress shop. He joined the ILGWU in 1920 and was part of the 1925 organizing campaign in Boston. It was his work there that led to his role as a business agent for the Boston Joint Board. He was later elected to the General Executive Board. He became manager of the Joint Board in 1932 and held that position until his retirement in 1973.
Series three consists solely of company files. These files help to illustrate the garment industry in Boston. The records are arranged alphabetically by company name. There is correspondence with the companies, but mainly they consist of signed status reports. Also included are contract agreements with the various locals. Many of the companies changed their names or went out of business, which is reflected in the records.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records
Arrangement
Series Meeting Minutes, 1929-1976
Series Correspondence, 1945-1970
Series Company Files, 1947-2000
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Women's clothing industry -- Massachusetts -- Boston; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Labor unions -- Clothing workers -- Massachusetts -- Boston; Clothing workers -- United States; Clothing workers -- Massachusetts -- Boston; Industrial relations -- United States; Industrial relations -- Massachusetts -- Boston; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Boston Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 12; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 46; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 56; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 73; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 80 (Boston, Mass.)
5491494
- Series Meeting Minutes, 1929-1976
  - Local 80. Minutes., 1929-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Italian
  - Local 12. Minutes., 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local 12. Minutes., 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local 80. Minutes., 1934-1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local 12. Minutes., 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local 12. Minutes., 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local 12. Minutes., 1941-1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 73. Minutes., 1942-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local 12. Minutes., 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 56. Minutes., 1947-1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Yiddish
  - Local 73. Minutes., 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 12. Minutes., 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local 73. Minutes., 1957-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local 12 and Local 80. Minutes., 1963-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Record of Union Membership. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 46. Minutes., 1938-1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 46. Minutes., 1940-1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 46. Minutes., 1945-1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local 46. Minutes., 1946-1955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local 46. Minutes., 1956-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local 46. Minutes., 1957-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local 46. Correspondence and Articles., 1943-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1934 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    January-June
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1934 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    June-December
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1936 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1937 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Joint Board Minutes. Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, and 80., 1975-1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    May 1, 1975; Sept. 18, 1975; March 25,1976.
- Series Correspondence, 1945-1970
  - Boston Joint Board. Correspondence. Philip Kramer., 1954-1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Boston Joint Board. Misc., 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Boston Joint Board. Correspondence., 1953-1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Originals Inc. Correspondence., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Boston Joint Board. Auditing Department., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Boston Joint Board. Endorsement Correspondence., 1954-1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer Invitations., 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer Correspondence., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Boston Joint Board. Board of Directors., 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Boston Joint Board. Misc. Correspondence., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Boston Joint Board. Century of Boston, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Boston Joint Board. Committee Minutes., 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Boston Joint Board. Politics., 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer and Dubinsky Correspondence., 1951-1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Boston Joint Board. Misc. Correspondence., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer Correspondence., 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Boston Joint Board. Union Election Materials., 1956-1965 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Boston Joint Board. Elections., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Boston Joint Board. Finances., 1953-1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Boston Joint Board. Correspondence Re: Fabric Salesmen's of America., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Boston Joint Board. Statements of Receipts and Disbursements., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Boston Joint Board. Contracts., 1962-1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Boston Joint Board. Girltown, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Boston Joint Board. Special Committees. Correspondence., 1945-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Boston Joint Board. Grievance Committee Minutes., 1956-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Boston Joint Board. Appeals Committee Minutes., 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer Correspondence., 1954-1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Boston Joint Board. Fairband-Hamlin House., 1960-1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Boston Joint Board. Rules and Regulations., 1946-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Boston Joint Board. Contributions., 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Boston Joint Board. Incoming Union Members Lists., 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Boston Joint Board. Arab-Israeli Dispute Information., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Boston Joint Board. Jewish Labor Committee., 1955-1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer Correspondence with John F. Kennedy., 1954-1966 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Boston Joint Board. Milton Kaplan. Correspondence., 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer Invitation Correspondence., 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Boston Joint Board. Misc. Correspondence., 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer. Correspondence., 1954-1957 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Boston Joint Board. Philip Kramer Cultural Center., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Boston Joint Board. Misc. Correspondence., 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer. Correspondence., 1962-1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer. Correspondence., 1954-1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer. Correspondence., 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Boston Joint Board. Agreements and Negotiations., 1956-1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Boston Joint Board. Collective Bargaining., 1949-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer. Correspondence., 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Boston Joint Board. Kramer Endorsements and Contributions., 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Boston Joint Board. Correspondence. Ernrico Parente., 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Boston Joint Board. Requests for Payments., 1956-1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Boston Joint Board. Misc. Correspondence., 1954-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Boston Joint Board. Union Employee Hourly Rates and Earnings., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Boston Joint Board. Misc. Correspondence., 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Boston Joint Board. General Executive Board., 1958-1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Boston Joint Board. Union Resolutions., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Boston Joint Board. Amendments and Special Committee Minutes., 1958-1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Boston Joint Board. Correspondence., 1954-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Senco Inc. Case No. 1-RN-635., 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ILGWU Campaign Committee Materials., 1956-1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Organizing Committee. Correspondence., 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Boston Joint Board. Correspondence., 1954-1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Boston Joint Board. Memorandum Agreement w/ Murray White Co., Inc., 1955-1965 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Series Company Files, 1947-2000
  - Aaron Coat Co., 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - A.B.C. Mfg. Corp., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Able Mfg. Co., Inc. (1 of 2), 1976-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Able Mfg. Co., Inc. (2 of 2), 1976-1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Advance Curing Co., Inc. (DBA Advance Pleating Co.), 1983-1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Alba Dress Co., 1947-1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - A and L Pleating Co., Inc., 1980-1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Andy's Sportswear, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - American Bazaar (1 of 2), 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - American Bazaar (2 of 2), 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Angela Sport Ltd./ Angela Sportswear, 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Annette, Inc., 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Anthony Sportswear Co., Inc., 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Apparel America, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Apparel Mfg. Co., Inc., 1982-1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - April Sportswear, Inc., 1983-1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - A and R Fashions, 1980-1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Arleen Fashions, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Arlene's Sportswear Co., Inc., 1979-1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - A and T Sportswear, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Avon Home Fashions, 1985-2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Baron Peters, Inc., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Barton Tailoring, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Bates Fabric, Inc. / STAPA-5, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Bayberry Dress (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Bayview Mfg. Co., 1976-1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - B.C.B., Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Beacon Garment, 1975-1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Bedford Mfg. Corp., 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Bedford Coat and Suit Co., Inc., 1977-1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Belle Sportswear Mfg. Co., 1973-1987 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Berkshire Coat Factory, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Berkshire Maid Garment Mfg. Co., 1953-1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Betcyan, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Beverly Rose Sportswear, Inc., 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - B and F Corp., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Bobe-Joe, Inc., 1983-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Bobby Joe Fashions (1 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Bobby Joe Fashions (2 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Bo-Mar Mfg. Co., Inc., 1980-1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Bomark Corp. (Klear Vu Corp.) (1 of 2), 1973-1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Bomark Corp. (Klear Vu Corp.) (2 of 2), 1973-1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Bonnie Dress & Sportswear Co., 1973-1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Boston Fashions, Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Boston Sportswear, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Bradley Coats, Inc./ West Haven Fashions, Inc. (1 of 2), 1981-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bradley Coats, Inc./ West Haven Fashions, Inc. (2 of 2), 1981-1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Bridgeport Lingerie Co., Inc., 1955-1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - The Brown Group, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - B and S Mfg. Co., 1966-1979 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - B.S. and G Mfg., 1970-1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - B.S. and G Mfg., 1970-1985 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Calvin Klein Sport, Inc., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Cal Mfg., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (1 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (2 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (3 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (4 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (5 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (6 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (7 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (8 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (9 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (10 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Camden Tanning Corp. (11 of 11), 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Capitol Swimwear (1 of 3), 1976-1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Swimwear (2 of 3), 1976-1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Swimwear (3 of 3), 1976-1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Car-Mal Sportswear, Inc., 1982-1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Carmela Coats, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Carousel Mfg. Corp.(1 of 2), 1973-1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Carousel Mfg. Corp.(2 of 2), 1973-1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - C and C Drapery Corp., 1974-1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Center Garment Co., Inc., 1976-1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Century Sportswear, 1980-1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Chadwick's of Boston, Ltd.(1 of 3), 1984-1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Chadwick's of Boston, Ltd.(2 of 3), 1984-1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Chadwick's of Boston, Ltd.(3 of 3), 1984-1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Charleston Mfg. Corp., 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Charmil Sportswear, Inc., 1981-1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)